



An **NTU chemistry graduate** with experience of conducting three research projects as part of my coursework, well versed in theoretical and practical aspects of wet chemistry, organic synthesis, chemical spectroscopy, etc. Worked for one year as an office assistant in a fish export company preparing **compliance documents**. IT-savvy with a "can-do" attitude.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Nanyang Technological University

Singapore

BS in Chemistry

Aug 2011 – Aug 2015

• GPA: 4.45/5.0

Went through a 1.5-year bridging course on English presentation and writing.

### **EXPERIENCES**

Office Assistant Guangdong, China

Freshwater Fish Department, Zhongshan Foodstuffs and Aquatic Import & Export Group Aug2016-Oct 2017

- Wrote documentation and SOPs on processing and transport of the food to comply with the AEO production standards of the China customs.
- Entered sales data to the company's ERP system and prepared invoices. Developed VBA and AutoHotKey scripts to automate the above tasks. Still in production.

### **COURSEWORKS**

## **Enzyme-responsive Nanovesicles for Drug Delivery**

Singapore

Honour's Project

Jan 2015 – Apr 2015

• Attempted to synthesize an ampliphilic molecule based on a  $\gamma$ -glutamyltranspeptidase (GGT) probe, a well-established cancer imaging agent. The molecule was supposed to form micelles that disassemble in GGT-rich malignant tissues to release anti-cancer drugs.

### PH-responsive Nanovesicles for Drug Delivery

Singapore

Small Honour's Project

Aug 2014 - Dec 2014

- Synthesized fluorescent amphiphilic molecules that were able to form micelles that release anticancer drug in acidic environment.
- Imaged the micelles with TEM. Determined CMC and pKa with UV-Vis and fluorescence spectroscopy.

### Study of Metal Cluster Fluxionality by VT-NMR

Singapore

Summer Research

*May* 2013 – *Aug* 2013

- Synthesized phosphine-substituted ruthenium clusters that showed metal-metal bond fluxionality.
- Carried out variable temperature 1H and 31P NMR to determine the rate constant of the fluxionality process through lineshape analysis.

### **PUBLICATION**

### Synthesis and Reactivity of Ruthenium-Antimony Carbonyl Clusters

Li, Y., Ganguly, R., Leong, W. K. and Liu, Y. Eur. J. Inorg. Chem., 2015: 3861-3872.

# TECHNICAL STRENGTH

Intermediate

Wet Chemistry, Chemical Spectroscopy, Organic Synthesis, Excel VBA

Beginner

HPLC, GMP, Photoshop